illicitencounters.com 2018-10-20

# Recommended Site - Married Dating UK - Illicit Encounters® - Extra marital affairs and dating

### What is your Privacy Policy?

This Website is operated by Illicit Encounters ®.

All data is owned and managed by Illicit Encounters. Illicit Encounters has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. 

All member contact and identification data is kept absolutely confidential and is never disclosed to other members or any other third parties.   

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website. 

**Personal Data:**

We never ask for your real name or address and recommend using a unique gmail address. If making a payment your name, address and card details are only for processing use and never held on our servers.

**Information We collect**

By using our site we will collect certain data from you for the purpose of operating the business and providing you with the service. This may include username (we recommend you do not use a name that can be traced back to you), email address, age, gender, relationship preferences as well as multiple choice information such as height, build etc. You should be aware that the information you freely submit in these boxes may reveal to us certain information that may be considered as sensitive personal information under applicable law.

We also endeavour to collect some technical information from you for the purposes of providing the service and for analysis. This includes device information e.g mobile, laptop etc as well as what browser or operating system you may be using. We sometimes collect this information using cookies and other technologies (see Cookies below).

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website, and to help identify you and your chosen set up of the Website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. 

_Cookies:_ Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your chosen set up of the Website, and to maintain a persistent session so you don't have to authenticate your login for every single page you visit on our site. We work with third parties that place cookies on our site to provide other services e.g. Ad targetting with affiliate companies (see Sharing of Data below), Analytics/Measurement (see Sharing of Data below).  

**How We Use The Information We Collect**

We use information collected as follows:

To provide you with the service and functionality offered on our website. This includes but may not be limited to: searching other members, electronic communication, authentication of credit/debits cards, data analysis.

_Electronic Communications:_ We may communicate with you by email with important notifications relating to the service such as notifications when a member has contacted you. We may also send emails offering discounts or news relating to the service. All of these communications can be turned on or off by visiting the '[My Account](https://www.illicitencounters.com/account)' section of the website. Additionally, every email communication has an unsubscribe link within it. We will never pass on your email address to any other party.

_Payment Information:_ When you use a credit or debit card or a digital currency such as bitcoin through our site, some personal information is required for processing such as name and card number. We do not store any of this information on our servers. The third parties we use may store this data. We only use third parties (such as Stripe and WorldPay) that encrypt the card number data that is stored. If you are an automatic billing customer an electronic token is used to communicate between ourselves and the third party in order to facilitate the future payments.

_Profile Deletion/Account Closure_ : Our site provides users the opportunity to delete their profile at any time by request to the online administrator or email to support@illicitencounters.com 

**Sharing of Data**

We do not share your information with third parties other than as described above and as follows:

We may share your information with our advertising affiliate companies. These are websites that promote our services and by use of cookies are able to track and measure the success for commission purposes. In these cases only user ID, payment amount, product purchased and payment date are recorded externally.

We may share your information with our Live Chat service provider (e.g. Olark). In these cases only limited information is recorded: User ID, Username, chat content and time of chat. This will only be applicable if you used the Live Chat service.

We may share your information with other third parties for analytical purposes (e.g. Google, Bing, Hotjar). In these cases only limited information such as User ID, gender, age range, device and browser, product purchased and amount are held externally.  

**International Data Transfers**

We use some data processors located outside the European Economic Area only after taking such steps as are required to ensure that Personal Data they process on our behalf receives protection equivalent to that provided in the EEA. Our processors are either certified as compliant with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework where they are located in the USA or have entered into an agreement with us containing the model clauses approved by the European Commission as providing contractual protection equivalent to that provided by the data protection regulations applicable in the EEA. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov](http://www.privacyshield.gov/).

External Links : This site contains links to other sites. Illicit Encounters is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

Public Forums : This site makes your profile available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Our Role as Data Controller and Data Processor**

We act as the data controller of your information. You can contact the controller by email to support@illicitencounters.com or by writing to The Data Controller, Online Tech Support Limited, 86-90 Paul Street, London EC2A 4NE

Illicit Encounters confirms that all personal data handled and stored by us is done so in strict compliance with the latest Data Protection Act 1998. 

Contacting the Website : If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please do not hesitate to [contact us](https://www.illicitencounters.com/contact).
